All right. Um, can you hear me?
>> We can hear you, coach.
>> Okay, good.
So, uh, don't have anything to give you
necessarily on injury. I think we came
out of the game, uh, injury-free, so
we're we're headed in the right right
direction there. Um, Trey was the only
one that was just working through uh,
his ankle, and we'll see how he does uh,
coming up here. But um for the most part
we we made it through. Okay. Anyways, uh
with that time's yours there.
[clears throat]
>> We'll start it off with Todd Lebo.
>> Hey coach, um heading into this this
last one, I mean, what uh what do you
kind of want to get accomplished with
Chris this week and having like an
actual full long week to get prepared
for a game because he hasn't quite had
that yet, has he? Right. He'll get a
he'll get the u a normal week in of work
and uh look forward to seeing what he
what he does with that. He he uh did a
nice job last week of getting everything
uh together and organized in his mind
and uh and was able to
manage the game well there.
>> We'll go next to Pete Sweeney.
Hey coach, uh we know that Patrick
Mahomes has uh gotten started on the
rehab process. I know you talked a
little bit about it last week, but just
generally speaking, how do you feel like
he's handling it and and can he be more
involved with the team this week?
>> Yeah, Pete, um he's around, so he's he's
in the building and and [clears throat]
um working doing his rehab and spending
a lot of hours doing it. He's he's
really attacked that and u and will
continue to do that. So, um, so he's
he's around and sees the guys and, uh,
but most of his time is, uh, being spent
rehabbing.
>> Does he make this trip to Vegas or will
he stay?
>> Yeah, probably not. Not Not this soon.
No.
>> Do you have another one? Okay.
Go ahead, Jesse.
>> Oh, okay. Uh, and I'll have a quick
followup, Sid. Hey, Andy, I know, um,
this little a little bit in advance,
but, uh, you guys are going to have a
top 15 pick for the first time in a long
time, and I know that's not the way you
want to get there, but, uh, how much are
you just looking forward to and and how
much can that help a team to to pick at
the start of the rounds uh, rather than,
you know, what you guys have done lately
with all the success you've had? Yeah,
Jesse, with Brett uh and his crew doing
it, it's uh that part's uh exciting to
to to see and what what takes place. Um
uh and something to look forward to. Uh
you're right, it's not where you want to
be, but it is where we are and and um
you know, we've got good people doing uh
the picking head headed up by Brett.
>> Great. And and I wouldn't think this is
any other way, but uh is Travis 100%
playing this weekend against the
Raiders.
>> Uh yes.
>> Okay. Thanks.
>> Okay. As it sits right now, we've got
one more with Matt Derek, unless anyone
else has a hand to put up.
>> Hey coach, kind of along those lines
with Travis, um would you imagine any
other starters this week that wouldn't
play? You know, I know Creed's got a a
streak start that he'd like to keep
going, but are there any, you know, the
young guys you maybe like to see just
get more playing time this week?
>> Uh, yeah. I don't The only one I would I
think is questionable there would be
would be Trey. I'm you know, he's got he
kind of pushed through that ankle and um
and he would probably push through this
game, too, but I'm I'm most likely going
to hold him back a little bit. And uh
[clears throat] so he just that thing's
been bugging on him for a while.
>> And I know you
>> that that would be probably the only
one. Yeah.
>> Apologize there. Uh I know you you've
gone through this every year for the
last few years, but you know, is there
any scenario that you can imagine where
you're not back as the coach next year?
>> Um
I no I'm Listen, I'm I think I'm coming
back,
right? If they'll have me back up, I'll
come back. You never know in this
business, Matt. So, that's a, you know,
that's a that's a tough one, but I I
plan on it. Yeah.
>> Thanks, coach.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.